{
    "general" : {
        "q0" : {
            "answer" : 2,
            "choices" : [ "Get rich or die tryin'", "Disappointment", "42", "Nothing" ],
            "question" : "What is the meaning of life?"
        }
    },

    "sports" : {
        "q0" : {
            "answer" : 3,
            "choices" : [ "Dallas Cowboys", "N.Y. Giants", "Washington Redskins", "Buffalo Bills" ],
            "question" : "What NFL team lost four consecutive Super Bowls?"
        },
        "q1" : {
            "answer" : 0,
            "choices" : [ "20", "22", "21", "32" ],
            "question" : "What jersey number did Barry Sanders wear in the NFL?"
        },
        "q2" : {
            "answer" : 2,
            "choices" : [ "Alabama Crimson Tide", "New England Patriots", "Philadelphia Eagles", "Denver Broncos" ],
            "question" : "This team won Super Bowl LII"
        },
        "q3" : {
            "answer" : 0,
            "choices" : [ "North Carolina", "Duke", "Michigan", "Texas" ],
            "question" : "Michael Jordan went to this college:"
        }    
        
    },

    "coding" : {
        "q0" : {
            "answer" : 1,
            "choices" : [ "Coping Skills Suck", "Cascading Style Sheets", "Create, Set, Start", "No such acronym in web dev" ],
            "question" : "In web development, CSS stands for:"
        }
    },

    "movies" : {
        "q0" : {
            "answer" : 2,
            "choices" : [ "Jamie Foxx", "Samuel L. Jackson", "Christoph Waltz", "Leonardo Dicaprio" ],
            "question" : "He won best supporting actor for his role in Django:"
        }
    },
    "music" : {
        "q0" : {
            "answer" : 0,
            "choices" : [ "Mark David Chapman", "John Wayne Gacy", "James Earl Ray", "Lee Harvey Oswald" ],
            "question" : "John Lennon was killed by:"
        }
    },
    "history" : {
        "q0" : {
            "answer" : 1,
            "choices" : [ "Boston", "Philadelphia", "Washington D.C.", "San Antonio" ],
            "question" : "The Declaration of Independce was signed in:"
        }
    },
    "science" : {
        "q0" : {
            "answer" : 3,
            "choices" : [ "Mars", "Earth (eventually)", "Mercury", "Venus" ],
            "question" : "Which is the hottest planet in the solar system?"
        }
    },
    "legal" : {
        "q0" : {
            "answer" : 0,
            "choices" : [ "This for that", "Quit while you're ahead", "I object, your honor", "No contest" ],
            "question" : "Quid Pro Quo roughtly translates to:"
        }
    },
    "highscores" : {
        "p0" : {
            "name" : "John",
            "score" : 0
        },
        "p1" : {
            "name" : "Joe",
            "score" : 0
        },
        "p2" : {
            "name" : "Jane",
            "score" : 0
        }
    }
}